2011年秋天 莉莉和马修从
In the fall of 2011, Lily and Marshall received
莉莉的祖父母那里得到了一份惊喜的礼物
a surprising gift from Lily's grandparents:
他们在长岛的房子
their house in Long Island.
莉莉和马修决定卖了它 只因为一个原因
Lily and Marshall decided to sell it for one simple reason.
它在长岛
It's Long Island.
我可不想在长岛过周六
I don't want to spend my Saturday in Long Island.
我知道 宝贝
I know, babe,
但房屋中介想用假家具布置房子
but the realtor staged the place with fake furniture
她让我们在开放之前再检查一遍
and she wants us to check it out before the open house.
好吧
All right.
最起码我们可以在假床上滚床单吧
Can we at least do it on the fake bed?
这还要问吗 你真让我觉得尴尬
I'm embarrassed that you have to ask.
所以 他们出发去了长岛
So, they headed out to Long Island,
当他们走进门时
and when they walked in the door...
我们要买下它
We'll take it!
我们不能买下它
We-We can't take it.
这房子就是我们卖的
We're the ones selling it.
我们要把它卖了 对吧
We are selling it, right?
宝贝 你祖父母把这个房子毫无保留的给了你
Baby, your grandparents gave you this house outright.
所以 在我看来 我们有五个选择
So, the way I see it, we have five options.
一 卖了它
One, sell it.
二 一年一度的鬼屋
Two, year-round haunted house.
三 用巨大的围栏围起来 黑猩猩保护区
Three, giant fence around the perimeter, chimp sanctuary.
后院已经有一个轮胎秋千了
There's already a tire swing in the backyard.
四 我们用大锤毁了它
Four, we destroy it with sledgehammers.
我喜欢四
I like four.
五 我们搬进来 抚养我们的孩子
Five, we move in, raise our children
让这变成我们的温馨小窝
and make this our family home.
直到他们毕业
Till they graduate.
然后我们用大锤把它毁了
Then we destroy it with sledgehammers.
全家人一起
: As a family.
不行 太疯狂了
No, this is crazy!
我们是纽约人
We are New York people.
我们有一个我们都喜欢的 又大又漂亮的公寓
We have a big, beautiful apartment that we love.
你说得对
You're right.
但那天 在莉莉和马修身上
But something happened
发生了一件事
to Lily and Marshall that day.
所有从外地回家的纽约人
Something that happens to all New Yorkers
都会发生了一件事
who return home from anywhere other than New York.
它们又大又可爱的公寓
Their big, lovely apartment...
哈 真奇怪
Huh. That's weird.
变小了
...shrank.
好吧 过完感恩节 我就要节食了
Okay, after Thanksgiving, I'm cutting out carbs.
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第十一集集
翻译： Cathy 安达小充 加菲猪 andie  ROY NO.2
后期： 霜之哀伤  校对： 园丁姐姐 henry
【HIMYM】字幕组出品
现在 孩子们 巴尼蜀黍这几周过得很糟糕
Now, kids, it had been a rough couple weeks for Barney.
首先 他背着女朋友和罗宾上床了
First, he cheated on his girlfriend with Robin,
然后他为了罗宾 和女朋友分手了
then he broke up with his girlfriend for Robin,
然后罗宾选了凯文 而不是他
then Robin chose Kevin over him.
所以他处境不大好
So he was kind of in a bad place.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗
You all right?
我有什么不好的
Why wouldn't I be all right?
哥又单身了
Barney's single again!
整个美国为之欢呼雀跃
It's what America's been clamoring for.
你刚刚经历了一次分手
You just went through a break-up.
通常人们这时候都会做些蠢事
That's usually when people do something crazy.
如果你是个女的 你已经剪了头发
If you were a girl, you'd have cut bangs
然后和你约会了
and be dating you by now.
向我保证你不会做蠢事
Just promise me you won't do something crazy.
我保证不会做蠢事
I promise I won't do something crazy.
别担心 他就要做蠢事了
Don't worry, he's gonna do something crazy.
实际上 我觉得我和女的玩腻了
In fact, I think I'm done with girls.
我不确定我是否还喜欢她们
I'm not sure I even like them anymore.
根据你这些年对她们做过的事情
Based on all the stuff you've done to them over the years,
我不确定你喜欢过她们
I'm not sure you ever liked them.
我是说真的
I'm serious.
得了 你爱死女孩了
Come on, you love girls.
如果有人和女孩玩腻了 那也应该是我
If anyone should be done with girls, it's me.
看看我这一年所经历过的
Look at the year I've had.
佐伊 维多利亚 淫荡南瓜妹
Zoey, Victoria, the Slutty Pumpkin.
现在我有点担心你会做蠢事
Now I'm worried you're gonna do something crazy.
我不会做蠢事
I'm not gonna do something crazy.
猜对了 我就要做蠢事了
And yes, I'm gonna do something crazy, too.
但女孩们 伙计
But girls, man.
女孩们
Girls.
-你知道什么疟了吗 -当同性恋吗
- You know what would kick ass? - Being gay?
当同性恋疟了
Being gay would kick ass!
一语中的 男人们互相理解
Word. Guys understand each other.
想像下 在一段关系中
Imagine a relationship where,
你们不会一直讨论感情
instead of talking about feelings all the time,
取而代之的是 玩疯狂橄榄球 吃披萨
you just play some Madden, eat a pizza,
互相幸福的抚摸全身
give each other a happy, roll over
闭着眼睛相拥在一起
and have some cuddle-free shut-eye.
兄弟 不管怎样
Bro, for what it's worth,
如果我们都是同性恋 你是我的首选
if we were both gay, you'd be my first call.
你介意打电话告诉马修吗
Would you mind calling Marshall and telling him that?
因为他觉得
'Cause he thinks...
不 这个假设仅限于
No, this is only in a scenario
只有你我是同性恋 马修不是的前提下
where just you and I are gay, not Marshall.
但如果我们三个都是同性恋
But if all three of us were gay,
你就会选我而不是马修 对吗
you'd pick me over Marshall, right?
如果我们三个都是同性恋
If all three of us were gay?
小姑娘 我们三个会一起好好乐一乐的
Girlfriend, we would all three of us have some fun.
绝对的
Damn right we would.
我们不是同性恋
We're not gay.
没错 还是离不开女孩
Nope. Stuck with girls.
我希望男人能自己生孩子
I wish men could have children
就像海马那样
on their own, like sea horses.
你说的和我想的是一件事吗
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
雄性海马有育儿袋
They have a little pouch.
他们就应该被叫做 海中的袋鼠
They should be called sea kangaroos.
不会吧 你想要孩子吗
No, y-you want kids?
我最近是在思考这个问题
Maybe I've kind of lately been thinking
关于娶妻生子的问题
about the whole wife and kids thing.
娶妻还是算了
Just minus the wife.
不用老婆就可以有孩子的
You could always go it alone.
就像《细路仔》里面的德拉蒙德一样
Like Mr. Drummond on Diff'rent Strokes.
对啊  但那可是80年代 那个时候 你可以不负责任地
Yeah, but that was the '80s, when you could just swing by
在豪华车上乱搞
any inner-city playground in your limo
然后把小孩带走
and scoop up some kids. - Mmm.
那真是个简单的年代啊
- Simpler times. - Hmm.
我想还是有一个人 陪着你比较好
I guess it's better to have someone
对吧 相伴一生
in it with you anyway, you know? Lifetime partnership.
我生命中 唯一能经得起时间考验的
The only partnership in my life
就是这份感情
that has stood the test of time is this one.
兄弟之间的感情
The sacred bond of man and bro.
或许我们应该一起组成个家庭
Maybe we should start a family together.
你在开玩笑么
Are you kidding?
这个地方可大了
This place is huge.
你看 我都能很嗨的在这跳舞
I mean, look, I can dance all crazy in here.
哦 糟了
Oh! Sh...
罗宾 听着
Listen, um, Robin,
如果我们感恩节到去东梅多过
are you okay with us all
你会不开心么
doing Thanksgiving out in East Meadow?
不会啊 我觉得挺好的啊
Uh, yeah, I guess that'd be nice.
噢 太棒啦
Oh, great!
在感恩节以后 我和莉莉打算
And then after Thanksgiving, Lily and I were thinking
就呆在那里不回来了
that we would just stay at the house
直到  你懂的
until, you know...
我们老死
we die.
什么
What?
不行
No!
你们不能搬到长岛去
You can't move to Long Island!
但是那个房子很棒
But this house is so nice.
它很大很干净 而且如果有小强的话
It's big, and it's clean, and if there's cockroaches,
它们会鬼鬼祟祟的出没而不被我们发现哟
they respect us enough to sneak around.
看看你自个说的话
Listen to yourself.
这又是孕妇思维在作祟了吧
This is Pregnancy Brain all over again.
不 我已经过了那个阶段了
No, I'm done with Pregnancy Brain.
而到了诡异的性幻想阶段了
I've moved on to weird pregnancy sex dreams.
长官
Officer.
你懂的 你一定懂的
You know. You know.
我只是在说 你现在的思维方式
I'm-I'm just saying, you're not in the right mind to be making
不适合做重大的决定
this decision right now.
你知道么 罗宾是对的
You know what? Robin's right.
我们现在不适合做重大的决定
We are in no state of mind to make this kind of decision.
谢谢 你总算正常了
Thank you. And now you're stepping off the crazy bus.
我们让宇宙来决定
We let the universe decide.
现在 你又疯了
And now you're back on board.
宇宙 你听到了么
You hear that, Universe?
如果你在接下来的24小时里面
If you send us a sign in the next...
给我们一个迹象 我们就搬去长岛了
24 hours, then we're moving to Long Island!
行么
Okay?
计时开始
Go.
嘿 你们听好了
Hey, guys,
再说最后一遍 这个地方空间是很大的
for the last time, this place is enormous--
噢
Oh!
天哪 你们到底有多少灯啊
Geez, how many lamps do you have?
这个想法太天才了
It's genius!
不用和一个女孩子结婚 而放弃路边的野花们
Instead of throwing away your life marrying some girl,
你可以和你最铁的兄弟合养一个孩子
you just go splitsies on a kid with your best bro!
我甚至不用
I wouldn't have to choose
在泡妞和养家糊口中做选择
between dating and having a family.
太对了 我可以带着孩子去约会
Hell, I could bring the kids on dates!
一个破碎的家庭
And a broken home?
那是什么东西
Um, what's that?
我们的孩子永远不会理解
Our kids will never know,
因为我们永不分离
'cause we're never gonna split up!
我们为什么要分开呢
Why would we?
我的意思是 当你的妻子走进家里
I mean, sure, when your wife walks in
看到你和一群空姐宽衣解带 你绝对会离婚
on you banging a hot flight attendant, you get a divorce.
但是当另一个奶爸走进你家
But when your bro-parent walks in on you
看见你和一群空姐宽衣解带
banging a hot flight attendant...
你会和这五根小坏东西们 击掌庆祝的
You get five of these bad boys, right up high!
你会加入到滚床单的大军里的 对吧
And you totally join in, right?!
-哦 不行 哥可是有底线的啊 -这就是底线啊
-Oh, no, there's the line. -That's the line.
我们找到底线了啊 真是好
We found the line. It's good we know where it is.
两位好
Hey, guys.
你们来了啊
- Hey! - Hey.
我们要宣布一件事
We have an announcement.
所以你刚才的意思是
So what you're saying is,
如果你们注定要去搬去长岛
if you're meant to move to Long Island,
宇宙中的一些迹象
some sign from the universe
会神奇的出现在你家门口吗
will magically appear at your doorstep?
孩子们 我并不觉得 当时有人敲门了
Now, kids, I don't think there was a knock on the door
但是为了剧情需要 你懂的
at that exact moment, but for the purposes of this story...
你们好 我是克里夫
Hi, I'm Clive.
我住在你们楼上
I live upstairs from you.
这个是你们的牌子么
Is this your sign?
我不知道啊 克里夫
I don't know, Clive.
是么
Is it?
哦 我们把它丢在外面了么
Oh, did we leave that outside?
恩是我们的牌子 我们要卖长岛的房子
Yeah, we're selling our house in Long Island.
太可惜了你们卖的不是这个公寓
Oh. Too bad you're not selling this place.
我想把我的公寓改造成复式楼
I'd love to turn mine into a duplex.
而且 我会给你们一个很好的价格
And I'd give you a really good price for it,
因为我很有钱呢
because I am so rich.
他没说那句话
He did not say that.
看看他鞋子就知道了
His shoes did.
好,我想说的是,我们得到这个迹象了
Okay, the point is, we got the sign.
我们这就搬到东梅多
We're moving to East Meadow.
我们开瓶香槟吧
Let's get some champagne.
就这样,莉莉和马修
And just like that, Lily and Marshall
开始了他们人生中新的篇章
were beginning a new chapter in their lives.
这对于我们来说就是…
Which meant only one thing for us...
我们要有娃儿了!
We're having a baby!
启动奶爸双雄模式!
Bro-parents activate!
-嘿 我们来给宝宝起名字吧! -巴尼…
- Hey, let's talk baby names! - Barney...
额滴神啊! 这也是我的首选啊
Oh, my God! That was my first choice, too.
不 听着 我们两个都喝醉了
No, listen. You and I are drunk.
这意味着领养一个孩子 在一定几率上
Which means there's a chance that adopting a baby--
无论他我脑海中的样子有多么萌
no matter how cute he is in my head
穿着小牛仔装 像骑马一样
with his little cowboy outfit on and he's riding our dog
骑着我们的狗狗 我们会养条狗的
like a horse and we also have a dog,
得是条金毛 不过无所谓了 它得是一条搜救犬
purebred Golden, but it's okay, she's a rescue--
可能不是一个好主意啊
might not be a good idea.
你太对了
You're right.
所以说我们回家 然后吃些阿司匹林
So let's go home, take some aspirin,
喝一肚子白开水
drink lots of water,
然后我们明天再看看 这还是不是一个好主意
and then see if it's still a good idea tomorrow.
这还是一个好主意
It's still a good idea!
必须地
It's totally still a good idea!
我们要有孩子了
We're having a baby!
孩子们 爹再强调一遍
Kids, I cannot stress this enough:
巴尼和我那个时候都很不顺
Barney and I were going through a tough time.
你们不能搬 就这么定了
You're not leaving, and that's final.
看看姐早上四点 在纽约城淘到了神马
Look what I bought at 4:00 a.M. In New York City.
一盘盗版的 超级流行的棒子电影
A bootleg VHS of a very, very popular Korean movie,
还有这个正品驴牌儿的钱包
this genuine Lenny Vintone purse
以及一个能给我搞来一个肾的 器官贩子的电话号码
and the number of a man who can get me a kidney.
有本事在长岛做这些试试
Do that on Long Island.
听着 罗宾 我们很感激你这么想要我们呆在这里
Look, Robin, we appreciate that you want us
但是那边才是我们想要的
to stay in the city, but this is what we want.
我说 你也知道的 对吧
I mean, you understand, right?
不
No.
这里有些有关于长岛的
Here are a few fun facts
小知识
about Long Island.
第一 从形状上看 它就像布鲁克林的屁
Number one: it's Brooklyn's fart trail.
所以巴尼和我
So Barney and I--
再重申一遍 我们那时不太顺
and again, going through a tough time,
怎么强调都不够啊
can't stress that enough--
找到了一个儿童领养的网站
found an adoption agency Web site
然后我们在线把表给填了
and filled out their online application.
巴尼?斯丁森
Barney Stinson.
泰德?莫斯比
Ted Mosby.
地址…
Address...
唔 填我在威彻斯特的地址
Oh, put my address in Westchester.
网站上的人希望看到我们将
They'll want to see we'll be
在一个良好的环境中抚养孩子
raising this child in a good environment.
郊区 你懂得
You know, the suburbs.
神马 不要
What? No.
-我所有的伙计们都在这里 -你的伙计们
- All my guys are here. - Your guys?
对 你知道 我是怎样找到那个为我打理好一切的伙计吗
Yeah. You know how I got a guy for everything?
他们都在纽约
Well, they're all in New York.
我的西装男 皮鞋男 票子男 夜店男
My suit guy, my shoe guy, my ticket guy, my club guy.
而且我要是没有某些专门的伙计
And if I don't have a guy for something,
我就会有个伙计男帮我物色个伙计
then I have a guy guy to get me a guy.
而且 其一大萌点就是 他就叫伙计
And oddly enough, his name is Guy.
好吧 这样吧
Okay, fine. How about this?
我们在周一到周五在城里呆着 然后到了周末
We stay in the city during the week, then on the weekend,
去郊区的那栋大房子
country house in the burbs!
这就是为啥 咱奶爸双雄可以有的原因啦
This is why bro-parenting works!
妥妥滴
Totally!
而且我的薪水加上你的薪水
And with your salary plus my salary,
这两个地方我们统统付得起
we can totally afford two places.
唔
Oh.
什么
What?
这么说来 你还打算要工作 是吧
So... uh, you're gonna keep your job?
罗宾 不用再说了
Robin, this discussion is closed.
老天要我们做这些事的 我们就照做了
The universe told us to do it, so we're doing it.
唔 老天爷也有犯糊涂的时候啊
Well, the universe gets it wrong sometimes.
还记得马修在犹豫
Remember when Marshall was trying to decide between
是当一名环境律师 还是在银行工作的时候吗
becoming an environmental lawyer and working at a bank?
这个故事很好玩的
That's a funny story.
那时马修受够了为巨人银行而工作
Marshall was fed up with his job at GNB and was
也想要辞掉这份工作
thinking about leaving it all behind,
所以他和莉莉认为他需要等待一个
so he and Lily agreed he should wait for a sign
老天爷告诉他该怎么做的迹象
from the universe to tell him what to do.
然后有一天
Then one day...
绝对的
Of course.
明摆着的 不是吗
It's so clear.
这不一直在那儿的吗
It's been right there all along.
我得给莉莉打个电话
I have to call Lily.
不好意思 不好意思 先森
Excuse me. Excuse me, sir.
抱歉 唔 我能否借下你的…
I'm sorry, but, um, can I please borrow your...
-埃尔尼 哈德森 - 怎么了
- Ernie Hudson? - Yes.
我能借下你的手机吗
Can I borrow your phone?
打给谁啊
Who you gonna call?
然后马修就成了幽灵克星
And did Marshall become a Ghostbuster?
那个消防局还杵在那儿待售呢
That firehouse is still for sale.
就连埃尔尼 哈德森都在求你不要打电话
Even Ernie Hudson begged you not to go through with that.
埃尔尼 哈德森真是个孬种
Ernie Hudson is a coward!
噢
Oh!
当然 我得上班啊
Of course I'm gonna keep my job.
为什么我就得辞职呢
Why wouldn't I keep my job?
我说 这整个叫建筑学的东西
Well, I mean, this whole architecture thing...
不最多就是一爱好吗
isn't it more of a hobby?
你说什么
Excuse me?
现在我们开吵了 我告诉你
And now we're fighting. You know what?
当我什么都没说
Forget I said anything.
不 不 不 不 不行 我们得好好谈谈
No! No, no, no. We're having this discussion.
当建筑师是我毕生的事业
Architecture is my life's work.
你为嘛不辞掉你的工作 我甚至不知道
Why don't you quit your job? I don't even know
你是做什么的
what it is you do for a living.
哥是做什么的
"What it is I do for a living?"
我上班啊 泰德 哥每天用上十四个小时的班挣来的钱
I work, Ted, 14 hours a day so that our baby can have food
来填饱咱们孩子的肚子 给他穿上衣服 让他住上好房子
and clothes and a nice house,
而你就只坐在一边乱涂乱画你的大楼
while you sit around doodling pictures of buildings.
这就是哥的工作
That's "What it is I do."
你知道么 去你丫的 老子去酒吧
You know what? Screw this. I'm gonna go to the bar.
哼 哼 是啊 因为你的答案总能在
Yeah, right, right, 'cause the answer's always
酒瓶底找出来
at the bottom of a bottle!
等等 等一下
Wait, wait, wait! Hold it!
大脑风暴 开始思考
Brainstorm. Brainstorm.
谁都不许辞职
Nobody quits their job.
我们找个保姆
We get a nanny.
保姆我定了
Dibs on the nanny.
不 不许上保姆
No. No banging the nanny.
泰德 求求你别深究
Ted, please don not dig in on this whole
‘不许上保姆’这个原则
no-banging-the-nanny policy.
好吧 我们请两个保姆
Okay, fine. We'll get two nannies.
一个用来上 一个用来照顾孩子
One for banging, one for childcare.
给“上”字画个重点线 两个保姆都是我的了
Slash banging. Dibs on both nannies!
你想想 泰德 你和我
Just think of it, Ted, you and me,
跟孩子住在一起
living together, with our kid,
我们两个火辣保姆 我们的宠物眼镜蛇
my two hot nannies, our pet cobra...
什么
What?
孩子需要一条眼镜蛇做宠物 泰德 别那么神经过敏
A kid needs a pet cobra, Ted. Don't be a pill about this.
而且我们派对一开就一个周末
And we'll have amazing weeklong parties,
到处都放着剑和忍者用的飞镖
and there'll be swords and ninja stars lying around.
那时我意识到了
That's when I realized:
跟朋友一起领养一个孩子 那是疯子
adopting a baby with a friend? Crazy.
跟巴尼一起领养一个孩子 二逼到家了
Adopting a baby with Barney? Freaking nuts.
我不能跟你一起领养孩子 巴尼
I can't adopt a baby with you, Barney.
为什么
Why not?
因为我们现在根本没有孩子
Because we don't even have one yet
你就已经成为一个糟糕的老爸了
and you're already a terrible father.
哦 我知道了
Oh, I get it.
你想要一个保姆
You want one of the nannies.
不行 她们是我的 不给你
Well, you can't have 'em! They're mine!
你只能再给你自己找第三个保姆
So you're just gonna have to get yourself a third nanny.
只不过第三个保姆我也预定了 拜拜
Except dibs on the third nanny! Good day!
感恩节到了
Which brings us to Thanksgiving.
马修 莉莉和罗宾一早就赶去长岛
Marshall, Lily and Robin were heading out
为感恩节做准备
to Long Island early to get ready.
天啊 怎么可能这样
Okay, how is this even possible?!
之前我们怎么拿进去的
'Cause how did we even get it in here?!
好嘛 我改主意了 分娩时我要做硬膜外麻醉术
（一种在分娩时用的麻醉手段 使产妇下半身肢体没有知觉）
Okay, I change my mind. I want an epidural.
你俩真疯了
You guys are crazy.
这地方大极了
This place is enormous.
我的意思是 看看四
I mean, look arou...
你们就没有听说过吊灯吗
Have you never heard of overhead lighting?!
你说对了
You're right.
我理解了
I get it.
这地方好极了
This place is great.
喔 那啥 卫生间在哪儿
Um, excuse me. Where is the restroom?
喔 就在那儿 很好
Oh. Right there. Oh, good, great.
我就是去那儿然后
I'm just gonna go in there and...
永远不出来除非你答应我你们搬回纽约
not come out until you promise never to move away!
家里有三个卫生间真好
It's a good thing we have three bathrooms.
嘿 巴尼
Hey, Barney.
那啥 那天我说你是个糟糕的父亲
Uh, listen, sorry about the other day
实在是对不起
when I said you'd be a terrible father.
你没必要多想
You had no reason to think otherwise.
我完全理解 我没疯
Totally understandable. I'm not mad.
谢谢
Thanks.
说实话
And, uh, let's be honest,
我们那时表现得确实有点疯
we were both acting a little crazy.
我觉得我们俩谁都没有真正准备好
I don't think either of us is truly ready
来承担抚养一个孩子的责任
for the responsibility of...
爸爸回来了
Daddy's home.
巴尼 你从哪儿弄到这个孩子的
Uh, Barney, uh, where did you get this baby?
嗨
Please.
你收养的
Did you adopt it?
切
Please.
莫非你有个孩子男
Do you have a baby guy?
难道是你的伙计男给你找了个孩子男吗
Did Guy the guy guy get you a baby guy?
泰德 我们该走了
Ted, we should get going.
不不不 我才不跟你走
No, no, no. I'm not going anywhere with you.
据我所知 我可能
For all I know, I could be
正在协助并唆使你绑架儿童
aiding and abetting a kidnapping.
嘘 奶爸可没发疯哟
Shh. Bro-daddy's not mad.
他只是爱吵人哦 他相当相当耐你哦 是的
He's just being a wittle loud. He wuvs you! Yes, he does!
- 这太疯狂了  - 你出门就感觉好些了
- This is insane! - You'll feel better outside.
- 来吧   - 不 我不能
- Come on. - No, I can't.
是吧快来
Yeah. Na-na-na.
接着我们出门了
But then we went outside.
噢 我的天
Oh, my goodness.
- 多可爱的宝贝啊  - 谢谢
- What a beautiful baby. - Thank you.
顺便说下 我朋友和我 我们不是一对儿
By the way, my friend and I, we're not a couple.
我们是两位单身直男
We are two straight guys who are single
有孩子的单身直男  就这些
and we have a baby. Just so you know.
看看这可爱的小姑娘
Look at this sweet girl.
嗨 我刚告诉第一个女孩
Hi. I was just telling this first girl,
我朋友和我  都是直男
my friend and I, both straight,
都是单身 而且我们有个孩子
both available, and we have a baby.
哎哟 这个小天使是谁呀
Oh, who is this little angel?
好吧 长话短说  我和他
Okay, real quick: me and him,
直男 单身 有孩子
not gay, single, have a baby.
我们应该考虑做个告示牌
We should look into having a sign made.
孩子们 再次强调下 我们那时候过的很糟糕
Kids, again, we were going through a difficult time.
但是这一段还挺好玩得
But this part was kind of fun.
啊 好可爱
Aw...! So cute!
太赞了
This is awesome.
对吧
Right?
罗宾 出来和我们谈谈
Robin, come out and talk to us.
我不出来
I'm not coming out of this bathroom
除非你们每个人都表现得正常点
until everyone stops acting crazy!
没人不正常
No one is being crazy.
再说一遍 剧情需要
Again, for the purposes of this story...
泰德和我有宝宝了 多荒唐
Ted and I have a baby. Crazy!
这是肿么回事
What the hell is that?
伙计们 这是 哈里肯・斯丁森-莫斯比
Guys, this is Hurricane Stinson-Mosby.
莫斯比-斯丁森
Mosby-Stinson.
你给孩子取名哈里肯（飓风）
You named your baby Hurricane?
这种做法
That is...
对孩子极度不负责任
ultimately inconsiderate to the child
她被迫带着这个名字过活了
who has to live with that name.
好吧 巴尼的孩子到底从哪来的
Okay, how the hell does Barney have a baby?
不知道 迷惑中
No idea. Super confused.
我觉得最好不要多想
I'm finding it best to just sort of go with it.
她可爱死了 有木有
She's super cute, though, right?
等等
Wait a minute.
哦 哇 哈里肯尿了
Oh, guh! Hurricane dookied in her drawers.
哈哈 小屁孩儿
Ha-ha! Poopy pants!
她需要换块尿布
She needs a new diaper.
对 尿布在哪儿
Right. Where do you keep your diapers?
我们没尿布
We don't have any.
你们没 哇噢
You don't... Wow.
好吧 我觉得我该去买点
Okay. I guess I'll go buy some.
你就要当妈妈了居然没有尿布
You're gonna be a mom and you don't have any diapers?
上帝 保佑那个孩子吧
Lord, watch over that child.
额 好的
Uh, okay.
来吧 宝贝
Come here, you.
呃 刚刚我听到有盘奶酪 在哪呢
So, there was talk of a cheese plate?
嘿
Hey.
要奶酪吗
Cheese?
谢谢
Thanks.
如果你不介意的话
If you don't mind me asking...
我可不可以问下到底发生了什么
what-what is this all about?
我是说 你是我认识最坚强独立
I mean, you are one of the most strong, independent,
不会在感恩节
non-locking-themselves-in-
把自己锁在厕所里的人之一
a-bathroom-on-Thanksgiving people I know.
为什么我们搬个家让你这么心烦
Why-why are you so upset about us moving?
也许我比你想象中更依赖你们
Maybe I just need you guys more than you think.
你是不是还有事没告诉我们
Is this about more than us moving?
这奶酪不错
This is good cheese.
罗宾
Robin?
怎么了
Yeah?
你觉得我是不是应该成为个幽灵克星
Do you think I should've become a Ghostbuster?
是个好主意 哥们儿
I think you made the right call, buddy.
好吧 泰德 我不想问你巴尼的孩子是哪来的
Okay, Ted, I'm not gonna ask you where Barney got this baby.
但你知道他为什么带个孩子吗
But do you have any idea why?
呃 几天前 我们在聊
Well, a few nights ago, we were talking...
呃 “我们讨厌女生 我们希望我们是同志”
you know, "We hate girls, we wish we were gay,"
之类的男人间的事情
just guy stuff.
然后我们大概可能也许决定
And we kind of sort of decided to...
领养一个孩子
adopt a baby.
嗯 这很荒唐
Yeah, that's crazy.
我知道
I know.
真的吗
Is it, though?
真的
Yes.
我知道
I know.
到底是真的吗
But is it, though?
不假
Yes.
呃 荒唐又怎样
Well, so what if it's crazy?
很久以来 我一直想遇见一个能和我组成家庭的人
I've been ready to meet someone to start a family with
但我总是遇不到
for a long time now, and I keep not meeting her.
巴尼是我最好的朋友之一 我们很少吵架
Barney is one of my best friends in the world, we rarely fight,
一旦我们解决了关于宠物眼镜蛇的问题的话
and once we iron out the whole pet cobra thing,
我们就是完美老爸了
we will be amazing dads.
为什么我们不试试看呢
Why shouldn't we try this?
你上次喂她是什么时候
When's the last time you fed her?
她在火车上喝了点根啤
She had some root beer on the train.
哦 泰德 我很抱歉
Oh, Ted. And I'm sorry,
但你真的不能给宝宝取名叫哈里肯
but you cannot call a baby Hurricane.
实际上 她的名字是赛迪
Actually, her name is Sadie.
詹姆斯 你来这里干什么
James, what are you doing here?
巴尼难道没告诉你们
Did Barney not tell you
我们要来过感恩节
that we were coming for Thanksgiving?
呃 没有
Uh, no.
那么估计他也没告诉你们
Then he probably also did not tell you
他在照顾我们的小女儿
that he was babysitting our new daughter.
这是你女儿
This is your daughter?
哦 谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
恭喜啊
And congratulations.
谢谢 来 爸爸抱
Thanks. Come here.
哦...哦...
Aw... Aw...
再见了 哈里...赛迪
I guess this is good-bye, Hurri... Sadie.
你的名字叫哈里肯 永远都不要忘记
Your name is Hurricane. Don't ever forget it.
我们过去吧
Go with him. Go on.
过来 宝贝女儿
Come here. That a girl.
嘿 泰德
Hey, Ted,
我听到了你的小演说
I overheard your little speech.
这确实不荒唐
It's not crazy.
十年前
About ten years ago,
我最好的朋友和我差点也做了同样的事
my best friend and I nearly did the same thing.
她单身 我也单身 我们都想要一个家
She was single, I was single, we both wanted a family.
情理之中
It made sense.
可现在呢
But now?
每一天 我们都感谢上帝当时我们没有那样做
Every day, we thank our lucky stars that we didn't do it.
因为她找到的她的丈夫
'Cause what she found with her husband
我找到了我的
and what I found with mine--
等待是值得的
it was worth the wait.
飓风这个名字超酷
Hurricane's a cool name.
是吧 汤姆
Isn't it, Tom?
宠物商店离得近
The pet store was closer,
我给她买了几片尿垫
so I just got her some wee-wee pads.
喔 对 还有这个
Oh, I also got this.
牛肉口味的 咀嚼对她的牙齿很好哟
It's beef-flavored and it's good for her teeth.
詹姆士 汤姆 嗨
James! Tom! Hey!
莉莉
Lily...
你没收到邮件吗
did you get the e-mail
那封我邀请
that I sent you about inviting
詹姆士和汤姆一起来过感恩节
James and Tom to Thanksgiving?
我发到你的CompuServe上了 你还在用那个邮箱呢 是吧
I sent it to your CompuServe. That's your main one, right?
感恩节快乐 老弟
Happy Thanksgiving, bro.
- 谢谢 嗨  - 嘿
- Thanks. Hi. - Hey!
我们坐下吧
Let's go sit down.
嗨
Hi.
好吧 让你知道了
All right, you got me.
詹姆士是我的孩子男
James is my baby guy.
可刚才的三个小时 太神奇了 是不
But these past three hours-- magical, right?
我们能这么做 快说 我们能这么做
We can do this! Say we can do this.
我们不能这么做
We can't do this.
不好意思了 兄弟
Sorry, dude.
我们得等属于我们自己的那个
We got to wait for the real thing...
无论多么艰难也得等
no matter how tough it gets.
是很艰难
It gets pretty tough.
我知道 兄弟
I know it does, buddy.
还有一会儿才吃饭 是吧
I have some time before dinner, right?
我出去  出去走一走
I'm going to go... I'm gonna take a little walk.
好吧
All right. All right.
我的老天
God.
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
我们还是朋友吗
Are we still friends?
希望如此
Hope so.
很好
Good.
听这个
'Cause get this.
泰德差点收养了一个孩子
Ted almost adopted a baby.
太疯狂了 对吧
Crazy, right?
那可怜的家伙最近过得不怎么好
Poor guy's going through some stuff.
他居然想把我也卷进来
He actually tried to rope me into it.
你能想象我当爸爸的样子吗
Can you imagine me being someone's dad?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
HIMYM字幕组奉献